{
    "id": "e7635bdf89774be7993db5af550afa41",
    "title": "Prepositional Phrases Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I would rather have coffee …………………… tea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "instead of",
                "instead from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… the rains, we went out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Despite of",
                "In spite"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… fire, break glass to escape.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In case of",
                "In case",
                "In case with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am standing here ……………………… my friends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in behalf of",
                "on behalf of",
                "on behalf"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We solved the problem …………………. a new device developed by our engineers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by means of",
                "by means",
                "by means to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….., I had a happy childhood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "On the whole",
                "In the whole",
                "By the whole"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you help me …………………… .?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in anyway",
                "any way",
                "in any way"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn’t allow cancer to discourage her. ……………………, she began to work twice as hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "On the contrary",
                "By the contrary",
                "In the contrary"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………, we are impressed with her performance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In general",
                "On general",
                "By general"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am seeing him in May – ………………….. in June.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "or rather",
                "in rather"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}